Number four, action item.
My MCRC Inter-8 Board of Directors conveyance of all assets to the city of Miami.
In contemplation of dissolution of my MCRC Inter-8,
an authorized resolution to transfer bank accounts.
I'm ready to make a motion.
Thank you.
Second.
Is there any discussion?
Yes, I have a lot to do.
I'd like to thank you for a lot of misinformation out there.
And this is more to everybody here.
There's a lot of misinformation out there about how we got to this important.
And the Board of Directors and the seniors and the business put in a bad light.
Everybody's wondering how we got to here and why we got here.
Everybody seems to think we're really messed up.
So I'm going to give you a sequence of the things that's how this comes back.
Back in last year, early this year, the field re-trived coming to the scene,
which is really pretty.
I mean, we still don't want you.
They come to us and offer this $10,000 to re-band this system.
We want to know what we wanted to do and they made us this.
What they wanted to do.
You know, it's really nice that the field re-trived and did that.
They were working on that and getting everything ready to go.
And then our funds went slow every month.
We decided that we had to get help.
We were looking for ways to find help money to keep this place going and keep it going.
One way to keep it going.
So we was told, I was told, I went to the city council meeting to make an angry report on what was going on here.
And I was told not to dismiss money at that meeting.
So I did not discuss money.
But we was wanting to talk to the city about helping us out.
So I made some phone calls to the city.
My phone call worked in.
So finally we got in touch with the city representatives.
And we was told that the city...
We didn't have the money and it's good to take it over.
We would be better off finding another part.
So if there were, we understood that we had to give this to the city.
We knew that I was.
We knew that we had to give it to the city.
But we told that the city didn't want it.
But what we understood is that we looked at all avenues that we could find.
We tried to find that.
What was going on?
What do we get to help?
Our logical choice.
We were going to try it.
We was going to give it to the help of dollars.
And I gave it to the open.
We talked from the end.
They said yes.
They were going to be more than we ever had.
So we decided to talk to the end.
The city made an appointment.
For us to meet with the chief and the few we were going to try it.
Docs represented in three more or four members showed up.
We expected the city council to be there.
Now I'm not complaining about the city.
I'm just telling you already.
Why we got to where we are.
Anyway, we come to the meeting.
There was no city representing there at the one.
And he made a phone call to find out where if anybody else has come.
Nobody has come.
So we went ahead with the meeting and I asked him.
That meeting.
So he had the authority to speak to the city and we was called yes.
So we continued with the meeting.
After he introduced everybody and we got the talk going.
The excuse yourself.
And said that we needed to work things out with Docs.
And the field where he tried to do it.
So we did.
Okay.
Fast forward a little bit.
The chief said, well, the best way to do this is to have.
So contracts grown up.
One of us.
The citizens of the city.
Because that's what was required.
And then we were going to have another round up.
And as soon as the city received it since they didn't want it.
Or understanding they didn't want it.
They would get it to the field where he tried.
Done it.
And we understood.
He grew up.
We signed our side.
We signed our contract.
But we did not vote.
To this loop.
This said.
Until the city signed their side.
Well, all the sudden.
Because all the misunderstandings.
The city said they wanted.
So that's how we got to that point.
Okay.
They didn't know that.
We was trying to do one of the right with the bylaws.
So now we are under a lawsuit from the city.
To do this.
This has all been one mix up.
And we from the get go.
We're just trying to keep this said going and keep it dry.
We was trying to do the right thing.
And it all got long out of the portion.
There is.
Time of misinformation.
Clothing out there.
So anybody.
how he got him. That is exactly how he got him. So I just wanted everybody to understand that.
It's not that we was trying to get it to the Indian tribes. We tried to get it to the
dogs. I had a talk to them. The dogs lay in a different meeting than the night of the
tree. She had stated to me that they had tried to take over her, run the scene to send her
a few years ago. And I asked her, she might be interested to take it over the end. She said,
they could, they didn't have money, they didn't have the manpower for nothing else. So that
the one avenue we had to just put out to the site we had already put out to the city. They
couldn't do it. So that is how we wanted to put it to the Indians. So there is a
Thursday story on how we got it. Now I would like to, and this is for the city. I would like to ask
the city, the law here. When we got to discuss this, this solution is the law system we have
against is going to be brought to that point. Or we need to get it in the current, we need to think about that.
I can't let it be that there is permission to respond to the question, just a solution is not
about that. So you're saying we, we, we can ask if the law system will be brought up on this
solution. The law system is not, I can tell you that my recommendation can be seen with the
that the law system you put it in the banks, you don't know, until we finish up this, this past program,
and the other one, that's a servo, and it's the bank. I think you can do it with the law system.
Okay, after that's done, the law system will be this week. If we, if we agree with that, the law system will be this week.
If we agree with that, the law system will be this week.
Okay, okay, that's all we do here.
I'm excited to ask you.
What's that deal with the second one?
Thank you.
Is that a word?
All right.
We know.
There's a child, a child, a grandson, a baby, a baby, a baby, a son.
We move on to the five discussion of my last senior student in the group, ready to
have an outstanding playing, to purchase this, and to play this.
because they are.
They are.
You know, have.
You've been.
You're going to be.
I don't.
That was a financial department.
You're going to be.
You're going to.
There's just regular.
Every.
None.
It's.
For the benefit of.
The.
To.
You.
A.
The.
I.
I think we're going to get some gifts and we'll see you soon.
I think this also will get some other gifts.
The only question we can do is I have a problem.
I have a problem.
Yes.
They think we're working.
We want to think we did respect.
And you said 99.
I was really, I think we were.
Many of the items that our Lord has wanted them to support the purchase.
They may be the handle that has been made or related to the file.
The important here on the model is if you need to absolutely remove the plug-ins, they're
pretty, pretty, pretty, pretty, pretty, pretty, pretty.
Well, they haven't been purchased that just did week and all this started to kind of put them
on hold and see what we're going to have.
So they've been funded on the proof we just had an order to put them in.
So that's on question here.
I think the fairest answer would be that the city council needs to set up a set up well on
use your order.
There's been some discussion in the United Way and it's also been some discussion that we're
going to do a play.
We're just trying to figure out where exactly we are to fill in the decision system.
So there's specific items, how many is there that gets this one?
One item.
Two, we're telling you about it, you can be fine if you don't want to talk about it.
What are we going to know about that?
We approve $10,000, we're going to pay for the report.
No, they're being made.
What sort of happens to the council?
I reckon that's what the council would be.
Just take that review and we have the council.
We're going to see what the council is going to be.
What's the council?
Anything else?
About one little table.
Three, three, four, three.
Three new full tables for 10,000.
Yeah.
And then while in 2000 the bid was 8,000, 80,000.
I told him not to really, 80,000.
But anyway, it's a gas.
That is the liver, shed a better, a greater hell.
The council comes with more table than the hungry.
And the cost to more fell in the year later.
We don't have room for money for that.
They're not mine for me.
And we do have money for that.
We don't know.
I don't know.
So that's for three, three new tables.
Not resultant.
That's actually three new tables.
Yeah.
That's three new tables.
Eight.
You're poor.
Three.
Eight.
Thank you very much for listening to this.
It was packed.
Oh, I see.
What did you tell me?
This is...
What are you talking about?
I'm going to check the motion to adjourn.
Second minute.
Second.
I don't know.
All right.
Hi.
Please.
I'm Frank.
There's our item.
Hi.
We're just going to be in motion here.
No.
Don't want to.
You said that.
I'm going to cut it back.